netted.net 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Netted

## Introduction

Recognition Media LLC strongly respects each individual’s right to personal privacy and we will only collect and use information through netted.net (“the Web Site” or “netted.net”) or our on-line newsletter (“Netted”) for the purposes set forth in this policy.

Note: This statement applies solely to information collected at or through the Web Site. However, we will frequently link to other online destinations, so we advise you carefully review their respective privacy policies. Please be aware that Recognition Media LLC is not responsible for the contents and the privacy practices of such other sites.

## Information Collection and Usage

In compliance with our mission statement to glamorize your Internet and e-mail experience, Recognition Media LLC collects personal information through the Web Site at several points. For instance, to subscribe to Netted, we require your e-mail address and zip code (this trade-off is truly bananas). Rest-assured, Recognition Media LLC does not collect any personal information that you do not expressly provide and will not sell, rent, or share your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes without your consent (that would be tacky).

When you visit our site, we also collect anonymous information such as your IP address or domain name to analyze site traffic, but this information is not personally identifiable. We will use this information to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

If you receive an email or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your Site password or credit card information) via email or to a web site that does not seem to be affiliated with netted.net, or that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information, and report the request to us at info@netted.net

## Review and Access

Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update, or modify this information.

## How to Unsubscribe

You can unsubscribe from receiving Recognition Media LLC emails at any time. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any Recognition Media LLC email and following the instructions. You can also unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link on the bottom of the Recognition Media LLC homepage and following the instructions.

## Third Party Advertising

Some of the window dressing appearing on our site may be delivered to you by our Web advertising partner or partners. Information about your visit to a partner site or sites, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, e-mail, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you.

## Cookies

An internet “cookie” is a small file which is placed on the user’s hard drive when you visit our site. It helps us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need some polishing. We also use cookies and the information we collect to show you relevant content and advertising. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

## Security

All of the information collected by Recognition Media LLC is locked away safely with our restricted database server.

## Modifications

Recognition Media LLC may make changes to this policy in the future. We will reflect those changes in this statement, so please check back periodically.

## Contact Us

If you have questions about this policy, or about the site, please contact us at hello@netted.net
